Alex Fallaw

Graphic Designer

I'm a graphic communications student at the University of Wisconsin Eau Claire. I've been passionate about art for almost a decade, experimenting with several different art forms over the years. I've recently gotten into coding, and I love the problem-solving and graphic design involved in coding a website. I'm looking for an internship or entry-level job in web or graphic design.

Skills

- Digital design
- Instructional graphic design
- Website design
- Wireframing
- Collaborative story writing
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- ❖ SketchBook
- ♦ HTML
- CSS

Education

- University of Wisconsin Eau Claire Graphic Communications
 2021-present
- Parkland College General Studies 2020-2021

Work Experience

Lowes Cashier

- Responsibilities:
 - Deliver excellent customer service at the register
 - Answer customer questions
- May 2021 August 2021
- Location: Champaign, IL
- Was awarded a service award for customer service

House Cleaner

- * Responsibilities:
 - Dishes
 - Vacuuming
 - General cleaning
- December 2019 August 2021
- Location: Champaign, IL